Ira Eaker Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part I: World War II File, 1937-1946 (Box I:16-36)
  - Mediterranean Allied Air Forces
    - Correspondence
      - War Department, 1944-1945
    - History, 1945, undated See also Part I: Oversize, (2 folders) (Box I:29)
    - Meetings, 1944-1945
    - Military missions, 1944-1945, (2 folders)
    - Press conferences, 1944-1945, undated
    - Public relations, 1943-1945, (2 folders)
    - Reports (Box I:30)
      - "Fifteenth Air Force - Operations in Southeastern Europe," 1945
      - "The Invasion of Southern France, August 1944," 1945
      - "Italian Campaign," 1945
      - Miscellaneous, 1944-1945, undated, (2 folders)
      - Prisoner of war interrogation, 1945-1946, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box I:31)
      - "Selection of Typical Attacks," 1944 See Part I: Oversize
    - Teleprinter conversations, 1944-1945
  - Miscellany
    - History of Allied Force Headquarters, 1945, (3 folders); (5 folders); (1 folder) (Box I:32, Box I:33)
    - Official travel
      - Brazil trip, 1945, (2 folders)
      - England trip, 1941, undated, (5 folders)
    - Passive defense plan, 1944 See also Part I: Oversize, (2 folders) (Box I:34)
    - Printed matter, 1943-1945 See also Part I: Oversize
    - Reports
      - "Air Operations in European War," 1939-1940, (3 folders)
      - "Biennial Report of the Chief of Staff of the United States Army to the Secretary of War," 1945
      - "Inspection of Target Areas in Germany," 1945 (Box I:35)
      - Miscellaneous, 1945, undated, (2 folders)
  - Miscellany
    - Reports
      - United States Strategic Bombing Survey, 1945-1946, (2 folders)
  - Northwest African Air Forces
    - "Air Power Over Italy," 1943, (2 folders)
    - Intelligence summary, 1943 (Box I:36)
    - Operations bulletins, 1943, (2 folders)
    - Rome, bombing reports, 1943
- Part I: Subject File, 1918-1960 (Box I:36-57)
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, military personnel "201" files, flight records, memorabilia, press releases, clippings, and printed matter.
  Arranged alphabetically by name or topic and chronologically therein.
  - Air Force, 1951, 1957-1959 (Box I:36)
  - Air Force Association, 1951-1959, (3 folders)
  - Air Force Historical Foundation, 1953-1959
  - Air mail, Army Air Force involvement, 1934, (2 folders)
  - Air service rosters, 1918-1928, 1947 (Box I:37)
  - Air training Command Advisory Board, 1953-1955, (2 folders)
  - Aircraft Industries Association
    - Aircraft Manufacturers Council, 1957, (4 folders)
    - Aircraft Show Committee, 1953-1954, (2 folders) (Box I:38)
    - Williamsburg conference, Williamsburg, Va., 1947
  - American Legion, 1947-1957, undated, (2 folders)
  - American Ordnance Association, 1957-1959
  - Army Air Corps, reports, 1927, 1935-1941, undated, (3 folders)
  - Arnold Engineering Development Center (AEDC), 1949-1950 (Box I:39)
  - Arnold, Henry Harley, 1948-1950, undated, (3 folders)
  - Awards and decorations, 1927, 1943-1947
  - Biographical information, 1940-1946
  - Boeing-Hornet transcontinental refueling experiment, 1929, (4 folders)
  - California Air Policy Conference, Los Angeles, Calif., 1948
  - Caribbean familiarization flight, 1940, undated
  - Citizens Committee on Rehabilitation, 1951-1957, (4 folders) (Box I:40)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1948, undated
  - Civil Air Patrol, 1951-1955, undated
  - Civil defense planning, 1950, undated, (2 folders)
  - Commission on Organization of the Executive Branch of the Government (Hoover Commission), 1948-1952, (2 folders) (Box I:41)
  - Congratulatory letters, 1942-1946, (8 folders)
  - Crusade for Freedom, 1950-1953
  - Defense Orientation Conference Association, 1952-1960, (4 folders) (Box I:42)
  - Early flight, 1940-1941, 1953-1954, undated
  - Fiftieth anniversary of powered flight, 1953-1954, undated, (3 folders)
  - Flight records
    - 1920-1934
    - 1935-1947, undated See also Part I: Oversize, (3 folders) (Box I:43)
  - Flying evaluation and pay boards, 1937-1940, 1947, undated
  - Functions and engagements
    - Mar. 1942-Feb. 1943, (4 folders)
    - Mar.-Sept. 1943, (9 folders) (Box I:44)
    - Oct. 1943-May 1946, (9 folders) (Box I:45)
    - June 1946-Dec. 1956, (8 folders) (Box I:46)
    - Jan. 1957-Feb. 1960, (4 folders) (Box I:47)
  - Greetings, 1942-1945, (8 folders)
  - Honors and tributes, 1945-1947, undated (Box I:48)
  - Hopper, Bruce C., 1944-1945, undated
  - Insignia for airplanes, 1937, undated
  - John Tracy Clinic, Los Angeles, Calif., benefit, 1957
  - Joint Civilian Orientation Conferences, 1951-1952
  - Lay, Bierne, Jr., 1938, undated
  - Long-range flight project, 1946
  - Memorabilia
    - Miscellaneous, 1939, 1945-1949, undated, (3 folders)
    - World War II, 1942-1945, undated See also Part I: Oversize, (3 folders) (Box I:49)
  - Military personnel "201" file, 1918-1947, (6 folders)
  - Miscellany, 1927-1930, 1941-1948, 1955, undated See also Part I: Oversize, (4 folders) (Box I:50)
  - National Advisory Committee for Aeronautics, 1947-1956
  - National Aeronautic Association, 1948-1957, (4 folders)
  - National Air Council, 1948-1951, (2 folders)
  - National Association of Manufacturers, 1953-1954 (Box I:51)
  - National Aviation Education Council, 1955-1956
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1951-1958, (9 folders)
  - National Security Industrial Association, 1949-1950 (Box I:52)
  - Order of Daedalians, 1955-1959, undated, (2 folders)
  - Pan American Goodwill Flight, 1926-1927, undated See also Part I: Oversize, (6 folders) (Box I:53)
  - President's Committee on Employment of the Physically Handicapped, 1956-1960, undated, (4 folders)
  - Press clippings, 1931-1959, (4 folders) (Box I:54)
  - Question Mark flight, 1928-1929, (3 folders)
  - Recommendations and commendations, 1942-1947, (2 folders)
  - Requests for autographs and photographs, 1942-1947, (7 folders) (Box I:55)
  - Returning war heroes celebration, Philadelphia, Pa., 1945
  - Scott Field, Ill., 1946 (Box I:56)
  - Texas Personnel Conference, Austin, Tex., 1948-1949
  - Transcontinental and Western Air, 1947-1948, undated
  - War games, 1930-1938, undated, (8 folders)
  - Wycombe Abbey School Foundation, 1951-1959, (2 folders) (Box I:57)
- Part I: Speeches and Writings, 1918-1959 (Box I:57-68)
  Articles, book drafts, and speeches prepared and delivered by Eaker, prepared by Eaker for others, or delivered by others and kept by Eaker as a reference file. Speech files also contain correspondence, clippings, and other material related to speaking engagements.
  Arranged by type of material and chronologically therein.
  - Articles (Box I:57)
    - By Eaker, 1927-1947, circa 1954, undated, (5 folders)
    - By others
      - Arnold, Henry Harley (prepared by Eaker?), 1940, undated
      - Fechet, James E. (prepared by Eaker?), 1931, circa 1936-1938, undated
  - Books (Box I:58)
    - Aeronautics, edited by James E. Fechet, 1940, undated, (7 folders)
    - Army Flyer, with Henry Harley Arnold, 1941, undated, (5 folders); (4 folders) (Box I:59)
    - Flying, by James E. Fechet, 1933[?]
    - Winged Warfare, 1940-1941, undated, (4 folders) (Box I:60)
  - Miscellaneous writings, 1943, undated
  - Reference material
    - Miscellany, 1918, 1925-1949, 1956-1959, undated, (2 folders); (5 folders) (Box I:61)
    - Speaker's manual, 1945, undated, (2 folders)
  - Speeches
    - By Eaker
      - 1934[?]-Oct. 1945, (2 folders)
      - Nov. 1945-June 1946, (8 folders) (Box I:62)
      - July 1946-July 1947, (8 folders) (Box I:63)
      - Aug. 1947-May 1951, (9 folders) (Box I:64)
      - June 1951-May 1954, (9 folders) (Box I:65)
      - June 1954-May 1958, (6 folders) (Box I:66)
    - By others
      - Arnold, Henry Harley (prepared by Eaker?), 1937-1945
      - Johnson, Louis (some prepared by Eaker?), 1938-1940
      - Miscellaneous (Box I:67)
        - 1927-1947, (9 folders)
        - 1948-1958, undated, (2 folders) (Box I:68)
      - Spaatz, Carl A., 1945-1947
      - Symington, Stuart, 1956-1959
      - Westover, Oscar (prepared by Eaker?), 1937-1938, undated, (2 folders)
- Part I: Oversize, circa 1926-1955 (Box I:OV 1-OV 15)
  Maps, drawings, plans, reports, and scrapbooks.
  Arranged and described according to the series, folders, and boxes from which the items were removed.
  - Part I: World War II (Box I:OV 1)
    - Eighth Air Force
      - Maps and plans, 1941, undated (Container I:21)
      - Miscellany, undated (Container I:22)
  - Part I: World War II (Box I:OV 2)
    - Eighth Air Force
      - Reports
        - "Bi-monthly Report of Bombing Results," (Container I:22)
          - 1943
            - June, (3 folders)
            - July
              - 1-15
              - 16-31, (2 folders) (Box I:OV 3)
            - Aug., (2 folders)
            - Sept., (3 folders) (Box I:OV 4)
            - Oct., (3 folders) (Box I:OV 5)
            - Nov.
              - 1-15
              - 16-30 (Box I:OV 6)
            - Dec., (3 folders)
        - Miscellaneous (Box I:OV 7)
          - 1943 (Container I:22)
          - 1945 (Container I:22) (Box I:OV 8)
    - Mediterranean Allied Air Forces (Box I:OV 9)
      - Correspondence
        - Arnold, Henry Harley
          - "Roundups," 1944 (Container I:24)
      - History, undated (Container I:29) (Box I:OV 10)
      - Reports
        - "Selection of Typical Attacks," 1944
          - (Container I:31)
    - Miscellany (Box I:OV 11)
      - Passive defense plan, 1944 (Container I:34)
      - Printed matter, 1943 (Container I:34) (Box I:OV 12)
  - Part I: Subject File
    - Flight records, 1944-1946 (Container I:43) (Box I:OV 13)
    - Memorabilia (Box I:OV 14)
      - World War II, undated (Container I:49)
    - Miscellany, 1955 (Container I:50)
    - Pan American Goodwill Flight, circa 1926-1927 (Container I:52) (Box I:OV 15)
- Part I: Classified, 1943-1946 (Box I:CL 1)
  Government security classified correspondence and reports.
  - Part I: World War II (Box I:CL 1)
    - Eighth Air Force
      - Correspondence
        - Eighth Air Force headquarters, 1943 (Container I:18)
    - Mediterranean Allied Air Forces
      - Correspondence
        - Office of Strategic Services (OSS), 1944 (Container I:31)
- Part II: Diaries, 1958-1974 (Box II:1-2)
  Handwritten and typescript records of daily activities.
  - 1958-1968, (11 folders) (Box II:1)
  - 1969-1974, undated, (12 folders) (Box II:2)
- Part II: General Correspondence, 1940-1981 (Box II:3-66)
  Correspondence and related material.
  - 10 June 1940-31 Jan. 1949, (11 folders) (Box II:3)
  - 1 Feb. 1949-28 Feb. 1950, (11 folders) (Box II:4)
  - 1 Mar. 1950-28 Feb. 1951, (12 folders) (Box II:5)
  - 2 Mar.-27 Dec. 1951, (12 folders) (Box II:6)
  - 2 Jan. 1952-21 Jan. 1953, (13 folders) (Box II:7)
  - 22 Jan.-31 Dec. 1953, (15 folders) (Box II:8)
  - 4 Jan.-29 Dec. 1954, (14 folders) (Box II:9)
  - 3 Jan.-30 Nov. 1955, (13 folders) (Box II:10)
  - 1 Dec. 1955-31 July 1956, (13 folders) (Box II:11)
  - 2 Aug. 1956-31 May 1957, (14 folders) (Box II:12)
  - 5 June 1957-28 Feb. 1958, (13 folders) (Box II:13)
  - 2 Mar. 1958-30 Jan. 1959, (14 folders) (Box II:14)
  - 2 Feb. 1959-29 Feb. 1960, (14 folders) (Box II:15)
  - 1 Mar. 1960-27 Feb. 1961, (16 folders) (Box II:16)
  - 1 Mar. 1961-12 Jan. 1962, (13 folders) (Box II:17)
  - 14 Jan.-31 July 1962, (14 folders) (Box II:18)
  - 1 Aug. 1962-18 Mar. 1963, (12 folders) (Box II:19)
  - 19 Mar.-18 Nov. 1963, (11 folders) (Box II:20)
  - 19 Nov. 1963-30 Apr. 1964, (10 folders) (Box II:21)
  - 1 May-30 Nov. 1964, (9 folders) (Box II:22)
  - 2 Dec. 1964-16 June 1965, (10 folders) (Box II:23)
  - 17 June-30 Nov. 1965, (11 folders) (Box II:24)
  - 1 Dec. 1965-30 Apr. 1966, (11 folders) (Box II:25)
  - 4 May-31 Dec. 1966 and 1966 undated, (11 folders) (Box II:26)
  - 3 Jan.-17 July 1967, (11 folders) (Box II:27)
  - 18 July 1967-31 Jan. 1968, (10 folders) (Box II:28)
  - 1 Feb.-9 May 1968, (8 folders) (Box II:29)
  - 10 May-20 Aug. 1968, (8 folders) (Box II:30)
  - 21 Aug.- 31 Dec. 1968, (8 folders) (Box II:31)
  - 2 Jan.-12 May 1969, (10 folders) (Box II:32)
  - 13 May-16 Sept. 1969, (9 folders) (Box II:33)
  - 17 Sept.-31 Dec. 1969, (9 folders) (Box II:34)
  - 1969 undated-13 Apr. 1970, (8 folders) (Box II:35)
  - 15 Apr.-31 Aug. 1970, (9 folders) (Box II:36)
  - 1 Sept.-30 Nov. 1970, (6 folders) (Box II:37)
  - 1 Dec. 1970-27 Feb. 1971, (8 folders) (Box II:38)
  - 1 Mar.-16 July 1971, (8 folders) (Box II:39)
  - 17 July-14 Oct. 1971, (6 folders) (Box II:40)
  - 15 Oct. 1971-14 Feb. 1972, (9 folders) (Box II:41)
  - 15 Feb.-30 July 1972, (10 folders) (Box II:42)
  - 2 Aug. 1972-14 Mar. 1973, (9 folders) (Box II:43)
  - 15 Mar.-28 Sept. 1973, (11 folders) (Box II:44)
  - 1 Oct. 1973-29 Apr. 1974, (11 folders) (Box II:45)
  - 2 May-15 Oct. 1974, (10 folders) (Box II:46)
  - 16 Oct. 1974-29 Mar. 1975, (9 folders) (Box II:47)
  - 1 Apr.-18 July 1975, (10 folders) (Box II:48)
  - 19 July-31 Dec. 1975, (9 folders) (Box II:49)
  - 4 Jan.-2 July 1976, (10 folders) (Box II:50)
  - 3 July-29 Nov. 1976, (9 folders) (Box II:51)
  - 1 Dec. 1976-31 Mar. 1977, (10 folders) (Box II:52)
  - 1 Apr.-9 Aug. 1977, (10 folders) (Box II:53)
  - 10 Aug.-8 Dec. 1977, (9 folders) (Box II:54)
  - 9 Dec. 1977-25 Apr. 1978, (9 folders) (Box II:55)
  - 26 Apr.-11 Sept. 1978, (10 folders) (Box II:56)
  - 12 Sept. 1978-31 Jan. 1979, (10 folders) (Box II:57)
  - 1 Feb.-21 June 1979, (9 folders) (Box II:58)
  - 22 June-24 Oct. 1979, (9 folders) (Box II:59)
  - 25 Oct. 1979-9 Jan. 1980, (11 folders) (Box II:60)
  - 10 Jan.-10 Apr. 1980, (12 folders) (Box II:61)
  - 11 Apr.-15 July 1980, (12 folders) (Box II:62)
  - 16 July-21 Oct. 1980, (11 folders) (Box II:63)
  - 22 Oct. 1980-2 Feb. 1981, (12 folders) (Box II:64)
  - 3 Feb.-31 Mar. 1981 and 1981 undated, (8 folders) (Box II:65)
    - Undated
      - A-S, (4 folders)
      - T-Y (Box II:66)
- Part II: Scheduling File, 1952-1982 (Box II:66-87)
  Correspondence, memoranda, agendas, invitations, programs, and clippings.
  - 1952 (Box II:66)
    - 18 July, Air Force ROTC summer training camp graduation, Long Beach, Calif.
    - 5 Dec., Arizona Aviation Conference, Douglas, Ariz.
  - 1954
    - 31 May, Memorial Day services, Veterans Administration Center, Los Angeles, Calif.
  - 1955
    - 16 May-6 July, European trip, (2 folders)
  - 1956
    - 27 Feb., World Affairs Council and English Speaking Union, Los Angeles, Calif.
    - 16-20 Apr., Air War College, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
  - 1957
    - 11 Mar., California Society of Certified Public Accountants, Los Angeles, Calif.
  - 1958
    - 26 Feb., Washington Society of Economic Analysts luncheon, Washington, D.C.
  - 1959
    - 20 Aug., testimonial dinner for Congressman Ovie Clark Fisher, San Angelo, Tex.
  - 1960
    - 14 Jan., 31st "Question Mark" anniversary/building dedication, Olmsted Air Force Base, Pa.
  - 1961
    - 1-7 June, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
  - 1962
    - 31 Jan.-3 Feb., American Management Association conference, New York, N.Y.
    - 25-28 Feb., Defense Orientation Conference Association meeting, Orlando, Fla.
    - 12 Apr., Tactical Air Command visit, Langley Air Force Base, Va.
    - 23-26 Apr., Strategic Air Command (SAC) briefing, Offutt Air Force Base, Nebr.
    - 24-26 May, 20th Pursuit Group reunion, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 30 May-2 June, Colorado Springs, Colo., trip
    - 6-8 June, National Strategy Seminar, United States Army War College, Carlisle Barracks, Pa.
    - 21 June, party in honor of Major General and Mrs. Keith Richard Barney, Washington, D.C.
    - 9-13 July, Hughes Aircraft Company advisory board meeting, Culver City, Calif., (2 folders)
    - 28-31 Aug., Hughes Aircraft Company visit, Culver City, Calif. (Box II:67)
    - 19-20 Oct., Falcon Stadium dedication, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 29 Oct., Air University dining-in dinner, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala., (2 folders)
    - 5-6 Nov. and 3-5 Dec., Hughes Aircraft Company advisory board meeting, Washington, D.C., and Los Angeles, Calif.
    - 13-15 Nov., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) advisory board meeting, Tinker Air Force Base, Okla., (2 folders)
  - 1963
    - 3-4 Jan., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Robins Air Force Base, Ga., (2 folders)
    - 3-6 Apr., Air Force Academy Assembly, Colorado Springs, Colo., (2 folders)
    - 10 Apr., Tactical Air Force Command (TAC) briefing, Langley Air Force Base, Va.
    - 3-5 May, Daedalian and Air Force Association meetings, San Antonio, Tex.
    - 10 May, Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) advisory board meeting, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 31 May-1 June, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 6 June, "Tonight Show" appearance, New York, N.Y. (Box II:68)
    - 14 Sept., Early Birds Honor Night banquet, Long Beach, Calif.
    - 25 Oct., Navy League of the United States, San Diego, Calif.
    - 28 Oct., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) meeting, San Antonio Air Materiel Area (SAAMA), Kelly Air Force Base, (2 folders)
    - 29 Oct., Elder Statesman Award, Aero Club luncheon, Washington, D.C.
    - 15 Nov., San Antonio Air Materiel Area (SAAMA) dining-in dinner, Kelly Air Force Base, Tex.
    - 20 Nov., Wings Club dinner, New York, N.Y.
    - 6 Dec., Muir S. Fairchild luncheon, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala., (2 folders)
  - 1964
    - 13-14 Jan., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) advisory board meeting, Ramey Air Force Base, Puerto Rico, (2 folders)
    - 11 Feb., Rome Air Materiel Area dining-in night, Griffis Air Force Base, N.Y.
    - 25 Feb., Strike Command briefing, MacDill Air Force Base, Fla.
    - 28 Feb., Purdue Conference on International Affairs, West Lafayette, Ind.
    - 5 Mar., Air Force Logistics Command, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio (Box II:69)
    - 30 Mar.-19 Apr., Japan trip, (5 folders)
    - 22 Apr., George Washington University class, Washington, D.C.
    - 2 May, Sylvanus Thayer Award to Robert A. Lovett, United States Military Academy, West Point, N.Y.
    - 15-30 May, Operation Desert Strike, Needles, Calif., (2 folders)
    - 4-8 June, Normandy landings anniversary trip, (3 folders)
    - 24-25 June, Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) meeting, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio, (2 folders)
    - 1-14 July, West Coast trip
    - 17-18 Sept.
      - Air Force Logistics Command Management Review/Commanders' Conference, McClellan Air Force Base, Calif.
    - 21 Sept.
      - Mobile Air Materiel Area (MOAMA) dining-in, Brookley Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 28 Oct., Middletown Air Materiel Area meeting, Olmsted Air Force Base, Pa., (2 folders)
    - 12-13 Nov., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) meeting, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio (Box II:70)
    - 20-22 Nov., Daedalian dinner, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
  - 1965
    - 11-14 Jan., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) meeting, Ramey Air Force Base, Puerto Rico
    - 6-24 Feb., Pacific air base trip, (2 folders)
    - 25 Feb., Reserve Officers Association luncheon, Washington, D.C.
    - 15 Mar., Air War College 19th anniversary, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 30 Mar., Inter-American Defense College, Fort McNair, Washington, D.C.
    - 30 Mar.-2 Apr., Colorado Springs, Colo., trip
    - 24-25 Apr., Alabama Reserve Officers Association convention, Montgomery, Ala.
    - 30 Apr.-2 May, Oklahoma Reserve Officers Association convention, Stillwater, Okla.
    - 7-10 May, Daedalian meeting, Kelly Air Force Base, Tex.
    - 21 May, Tactical Air Command (TAC) briefing, Langley Air Force Base, Va.
    - 27 May, Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 28 May, Lowry Air Force Base dining-in, Lowry Air Force Base, Colo.
    - 4-5, 8-9 June, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 27 July, JANUS party, Army and Navy Club, Washington, D.C.
    - 29-31 July, Mark Bradley's retirement, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 3-8 Sept., Operation WONDRA ISLE, Rainy Lake, Ontario, Canada
    - 13-14 Oct., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Offutt Air Force Base, Nebr.
    - 22-24 Oct., Arnold Air Society meeting, Los Angeles, Calif.
    - 29 Oct., Ogden Air Materiel Area (OGAMA) dining-in, Hill Air Force Base, Utah (Box II:71)
    - 9-19 Nov., European trip
    - 19-20 Nov., History of Aviation project meeting, University of Texas, Austin, Tex.
    - 25 Nov.-3 Dec., Los Angeles, Calif., trip
    - 10 Dec., Oklahoma City Chamber of Commerce forum, Oklahoma City, Okla., (2 folders)
  - 1966
    - 10-11 Jan., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 25 Jan., Okmulgee Chamber of Commerce, Okmulgee, Okla.
    - 20-25 Mar., Air Force Association conference, Dallas, Tex.
    - 26 Mar., Daedalian dining-in, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 6-7 Apr., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 28 Apr.-2 May, Daedalian annual convention, Kelly Air Force Base, Tex.
    - 15 May, Sylvanus Thayer election to Hall of Fame, New York, N.Y.
    - 16-20 May, National security forum, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala., (2 folders)
    - 22-24 May, Military Air Lift Command briefing, Scott Air Force Base, Ill.
    - 25-27 May, Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Hill Air Force Base, Utah
    - 3-8 June, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo., (2 folders)
    - 5 July, Wichita Chamber of Commerce luncheon, Wichita, Kans., (2 folders) (Box II:72)
    - 13-14 July, Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 7-9 Sept., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 15 Sept., McGuire Air Force Base dining-in, McGuire Air Force Base, N.J.
    - 1 Oct., Falcon Foundation meeting, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 22 Oct., Reserve Officers Association, El Paso, Tex.
    - 26-28 Oct., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Tinker Air Force Base, Okla.
    - 25 Nov., Tactical Air Command (TAC) briefing, Langley Air Force Base, Va.
    - 6 Dec., Louisiana State University, Air Force Reserve Officers Training Corps, Air Force Day, Baton Rouge, La.
    - 7 Dec., Reserve Officers Association, San Antonio, Tex., (2 folders)
    - 12-14 Dec., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Kelly Air Force Base, Tex.
  - 1967
    - 14 Feb., Ground Electronics Engineering Installations Agency (GEEIA) dining-in, Orlando, Fla., (2 folders)
    - 15 Feb., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Ramey Air Force Base, Puerto Rico
    - 24 Feb., 22nd Air Force dining-in, Travis Air Force Base, Calif.
    - 25 Feb., Sacramento Air Materiel Area (SMAMA) dining-in, McClellan Air Force Base, Calif. (Box II:73)
    - 14 Mar., Air National Guard Convention, San Francisco, Calif.
    - 31 Mar.-2 Apr., Air Force Academy meeting re cemetery gate, Colorado Springs, Colo., 1966-1967, undated See also Part II: Oversize
    - 5 Apr., Warner Robins Air Materiel Area (WRAMA) dining-in, Robins Air Force Base, Ga.
    - 11-13 Apr., Air Force Systems Command orientation tour, Andrews Air Force Base, Washington, D.C., (2 folders)
    - 18-20 Apr., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Warner Robins Air Materiel Area (WRAMA), Robins Air Force Base, Ga.
    - 26-28 Apr., Daedalian convention and visit to Randolph Air Force Base, Tex.
    - 29 Apr., Reserve Officers Association, Department of Indiana, Indianapolis, Ind., 1966-1967, undated
    - 2-5 May, Tactical Air Command (TAC) Career Motivation Conference, Langley Air Force Base, Va., (3 folders)
    - 9 May, Air Force "Senior Statesmen" Conference, Washington, D.C.
    - 17 May, Quarter Century Club, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 27 May, Air Force Mid-Year conference, Santa Monica, Calif.